(Bernadette:)...I probably would have gone
into physics or ice dancing.
(Leonard:)My tests of the Aharonov-Bohm
quantum interference effect...
(Leonard:)...have reached an interesting point.
We're testing phase shift
due to electric potential.
(Bernadette:)-That's amazing.
SHELDON [CHUCKLES]: Yes.
(Sheldon:)Leonard's work is nearly
as amazing as third graders...
(Sheldon:)...growing lima beans
in wet paper towels.
While I appreciate the "oh, snap"...
(Sheldon:)...I'm uncomfortable having
your moist breath in my ear.
(Bernadette:)Are you going to try to set up
the voltages using tunnel junctions?
(Leonard:)Yes, I am.
-Wanna see a simulation on my laptop?
-Oh, yeah. Show me.
(Bernadette:)In microbiology, the most exciting thing
I get to work with is yeast.
SHELDON: Howard?
-Yeah?
(Sheldon:)Your shoes are delightful.
(Sheldon:)Where did you get them?
(Bernadette:)-What?
-Buzzinga. I don't care.